var questions = [
   {
   
    question: "1.Which is my favorite Sport of all time?\nA.Football\nB.Cricket\nC.Badminton\nD.Baseball\n Your answer: ", 
   answer: ["B","Cricket"]
  },
   {
     question: "2.Which of the following is my supporting IPL team since 2008?\nA.CSK\nB.RR\nC.PBKS\nD.RCB\nYour answer: ",
     answer: ["D","RCB"]
    
   },
   { 
    question: "3.Which of the following to which I am Scared of ?\nA.Cockroach\nB.Lizard\nC.Dog\nD.None of these\nYour answer: ",
     answer: ["A","Cockroach"]
   },

  {
    question: "4.Which of the following I am fond of ?\nA.Sport Car\nB.Sport bike\nC.Royal Enfield Bullet\nD.90's Scooter\nYour answer: ",
    answer: ["B","Sport bike"]
  },

   {
     question: "5.What is that thing which always cheers me up after a defeat ?\nA.Self confidence and motivation \nB.Remembering about my special person's struggle\nC.By Spending time with the one whom I love\nD.All of the above\nYour answer: ",
    answer: ["D","All of the above"]
   },
 {
   question: "6.Which of the following I would choose ?\nA.Cricket\nB.Late night Driving Car at high speed\nC.Coding\nD.Watching Horror movie \nYour answer: ",
   answer: ["B" , "Late night Driving Car at high speed"]
  },

  {
   question: "7.How many siblings do I have ?\nA.1\nB.2\nC.3\nD.4\nYour answer: ",
    answer: ["A","1"] 
  },
  

{
  question: "8.My birthdy is on ?\nA.30th August\nB.30th September\nC.30th October\nD.30th November\nYour answer: ",
    answer: ["A", "30th August"]
},

{
  question: "9.Which is my favorite food type?\nA.Italian\nB.Chinese\nC.Gujarati\nD.Punjabi\nYour answer: ",
    answer: ["B", "Chinese"]

},

{
  question: "10.Who is my role model?\nA.Chris Gayle\nB.Abraham Benjamin Devillers\nC.Ronaldo\nD.Virat Kohli\nYour answer: ",
    answer: ["D", "Virat Kohli"]
},
]



module.exports = questions